<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chocolate on TECHATPARK - BUILDING PRO-GRAMMERS !</title>
    <link>/tags/chocolate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in chocolate on TECHATPARK - BUILDING PRO-GRAMMERS !</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/tags/chocolate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post No. 1</title>
      <link>/our-achievements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-achievements/</guid>
      <description>Empowering the Underprivileged
TECH@PARK is a volunteer organization that helps underprivileged freshers find software jobs. Our mission is to empower individuals from disadvantaged backgrounds by providing them with the necessary skills to succeed in the IT industry.
Our Achievements: More than 80% of our students are first-generation engineers of their families. By providing them with quality training and job placement assistance, we are not only helping them but also their families and future generations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post No. 1</title>
      <link>/our-method/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-method/</guid>
      <description>TECH@PARK is a volunteer organization that helps underprivileged freshers find software jobs. The organization has a unique approach to training that sets it apart from others. Picking a Candidate TECH@PARK identifies potential candidates through trusted sources, such as colleagues and ex-students, who know the candidate&#39;s potential personally. The organization then interviews candidates based on certain parameters to determine if they have the potential to succeed in the IT industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post No. 1</title>
      <link>/our-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-values/</guid>
      <description>TECH@PARK is a non-profit organization that is committed to empowering underprivileged freshers by providing them with training and resources to succeed in the IT industry. Our approach to training is unique and designed to produce top-quality talents who are valuable assets to any hirer. Our students are chosen based on their potential, trained by industry experts, and are technically productive from day one. As a result, TECH@PARK alumni are highly sought-after by employers, making them an excellent addition to any team.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
